Guide to the American Journal of Psychology records,1948-1965.
American Journal of Psychology records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
American Journal of Psychology records, 1948-1965.
2997
31 cubic ft.
Manuscripts and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Working papers (manuscripts and correspondence) of individual issues of the American Journal of Psychology. Includes Karl Dallenbach - Edwin G. Boring correspondence.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Working papers (manuscripts and correspondence) of individual issues of the American Journal of Psychology. Includes Karl Dallenbach - Edwin G. Boring correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Boring, Edwin Garrigues, 1886-1968.; Dallenbach, Karl M.
Subjects:
Psychology.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Related collection: Karl M. Dallenbach. Papers, #2958.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Chronological by date of issue.
CONTAINER LIST
- Apr., July, Oct. 1948 (Box 1)
- Jan., Apr. 1949 (Box 2)
- July, Oct. 1949; Jan., Apr. 1950 (Box 3)
- July, Oct. 1959; Jan. 1951 (Box 4)
- Apr., July 1951 (Box 5)
- Oct. 1951; Jan. 1952 (Box 6)
- Apr., July 1952 (Box 7)
- Oct. 1952; Jan. 1953 (Box 8)
- Apr., July 1953 (Box 9)
- Oct. 1953; Mar. 1954 (Box 10)
- June, Sept. 1954 (Box 11)
- Dec. 1954; Mar., June 1955 (Box 12)
- Sept., Dec. 1955 (Box 13)
- Mar., June 1956 (Box 14)
- Sept., Dec. 1956 (Box 15)
- Mar., June 1957 (Box 16)
- Sept., Dec. 1957 (Box 17)
- Mar., June 1958 (Box 18)
- Sept., Dec. 1958 (Box 19)
- Mar., June 1959 (Box 20)
- Sept., Dec. 1959; Mar. 1960 (Box 21)
- June, Sept. 1960 (Box 22)
- Mar. 1961; Dec. 1960 (Box 23)
- June, Sept. 1961 (Box 24)
- Dec. 1961; Mar. 1962 (Box 25)
- June, Sept. 1962 (Box 26)
- Dec. 1962; Mar., June 1963 (Box 27)
- Sept., Dec. 1963; Mar. 1964 (Box 28)
- June, Sept. 1964 (Box 29)
- Mar., June, Sept. 1965 (Box 30)
- Dec. 1965 (Box 31)